location: svg-inline--fa fa-map-marker fa-w-12
tel: svg-inline--fa fa-phone fa-w-16
href="tel:1900.63.69.36"
mail: svg-inline--fa fa-envelope fa-w-16
href="mailto:info@tocotocotea.com"
facebook: svg-inline--fa fa-facebook fa-w-14
insta: svg-inline--fa fa-instagram fa-w-14
youtube: svg-inline--fa fa-youtube fa-w-18
twitter: svg-inline--fa fa-twitter fa-w-16
gg: svg-inline--fa fa-google-plus fa-w-16